(Leonard:)Wait, that's it?
I thought we had a whole hour.
(Leonard:)Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
My name is Dr. Leonard Hofstadter.
It is my great honor
to introduce the winner...
(Leonard:)...of this year's Chancellor's Award
for Science, and my good friend...
(Leonard:)...Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
[APPLAUSE]
(Leonard:)But before I do,
I'd like to share with you a letter...
(Leonard:)...from Sheldon's mother,
who couldn't be here tonight.
(Leonard:)Isn't that nice?
His mother sent him a letter.
(Leonard:)She's proud of him.
(Leonard:)Wonder what that feels like.
"Dear Shelly."
(Leonard:)That's what she calls him.
Shelly. It's a pet name.
(Leonard:)You know what my mother's
pet name for me is? Leonard.
(Leonard:)But I digress.
-"Dear Shelly, I am so proud..."
-Oh, dear.
(Penny:)-What's the matter?
-I'm getting dizzy.
(Raj:)Don't worry.
You're surrounded by your C-Men.